The crisp air of autumn settled over the yard, bringing with it falling leaves and a quiet calm.
A golden carpet gathered at the foot of the old tree, rustling secrets in the breeze.
Suddenly, a little head poked through the pile... it was Pip, the hedgehog, ready for adventure!
He scampered out, his nose twitching, searching for something special in the grass.
Up the sturdy trunk he went, climbing high to get a better view, a hopeful smile on his face.
And there, nestled amongst the leaves below, was little Nutmeg, the acorn, who had taken a tumble.
Pip saw his friend and hurried back down.
He found Nutmeg looking a little bruised from the fall.
Pip leaned in, gently nudging his friend.
A little bandage helped make everything better.
Together, they found warmth and comfort in the soft pile of leaves, two friends ready for whatever autumn brought.
Meanwhile, deep in the woods, Barnaby the badger was settling in for a cozy night by the fire.