Autumn arrives...
...and the leaves begin to fall, gathering in soft piles on the ground.
Out from the rustling depths, a small creature stirred.
A little hedgehog, venturing out into the crisp air.
He looked around, a gentle smile on his face, ready for adventure.
High above, he climbed the sturdy branches of the old tree.
From his perch, he surveyed the world below.
And there, nestled amongst the scattered leaves, he saw something...
...something small, and perhaps, a little lost.
He carefully descended, drawn to the tiny figure.
An acorn! But this little acorn had a small boo-boo.
A bandage, carefully placed, a sign of a recent tumble.
Finding comfort in each other's company, the hedgehog and the acorn settled in, friends found in the autumn leaves.
Meanwhile, in the heart of the woods...
...a solitary badger made camp, the fire casting a warm glow against the gathering dusk.